ROBERT TESTA

32 46th Street Weehawken, NJ 07086 (732) 979 - 7722 RKTesta@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Decisive Marketing Director who drives company growth through creative and innovative marketing strategies and sales tactics. Skilled expert on both online and direct marketing campaign strategies, implying a solid understanding of digital marketing, including SEO, PPC, SEM and Social Media marketing.

SKILLS

MARKETING & SALES: Conducted direct response marketing promotions that boosted business by 69 percent. Increased patient volume by 144 percent. Raised online engagement and awareness by 285 percent.

SEO/SEM: Created and implemented multiple SEO/SEM straegies such as landing pages, Google Adwords, and Social Media in order to increase online presence. Closely monitor all organic and paid traffic to identify areas of performance and opportunity.

MANAGEMENT: Managed multiple offices cooperatively. Controlled and prioritized multiple projects simultaneously. Reduced marketing expenses by 19 percent.

EXPERIENCE

Marketing Director

October 2013 - Current

Bergen Medical Sports & Spine, Paramus, NJ

- Liaison between 60+ physicians and doctors offices.
- Identified, developed and evaluated marketing strategies based on knowledge of company objectives and market trends.
- Promoted brand awareness with SEO/SEM optimization, attractive web design.

Marketing Manager

July 2012 - October 2013

I T Global Protech, Rochelle Park, NJ

- Created sales strategies to promote advertising offerings and motivate larger
- Initiated and managed all traditional and digital marketing campaigns.
- Made strategic connections with other business's in order to increase sales

Social Media and Marketing Intern

May 2012 - June 2013

SituatioNormal, Montclair, NJ

- Developed innovative marketing solutions grounded in a clear understanding of clients needs.
- Created and managed clients social media accounts, which include Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, and Instagram.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Marketing

Montclair State University, Montclair, NJ, graduated May 2013

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Montclair State University's 2012 Entrepreneur of the Year
- Created & Studied Abroad in Chile's International Study Program
- Completed MSU's CEO Training Program